Whether you're new to international shipping or you're a seasoned expert, it's
good to consider how you'll ship and fulfill international orders.
In this
step, you'll learn the different ways Amazon can help with shipping globally.
Let's explore your options.
One, you can ship and fulfill yourself.
Two, you can
enlist Amazon services to take care of inbounding, exporting, and other
international fulfillment operations.
Or three, you can do a combination of both.
You ship and fulfill some products, and Amazon ships and fulfills some.
Amazon's fulfillment services make managing international sales easier, and
our global fulfillment networks ensure customers receive products quickly.
Also,
FBA works similarly in all of Amazon's global marketplaces, where products
fulfilled by Amazon are generally eligible for prime, and thus more appealing to
prime customers around the world.
Wave goodbye to complex global processes and
say hello to convenient global shipping.
It's time to set sail with the help of
Amazon global selling.